# **Benjamin Hinora**

Senior Web & Mobile Developer, Web3 Developer

#### **CONTACT INFORMATION**

Email: benjaminhinora@gmail.com

Phone: (705) 990-2520

Link: https://www.linkedin.com/in/benjamin-hinora

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a senior full stack developer with more than 8 years of strong experience in website and webapp development using modern JS frameworks and libraries including React, Redux(saga | thunk), React Hooks, Angular, Vue, and Node/Express. I am also pretty much familiar with AWS, GCP, Heroku and AWS Amplify. Recently worked on several Blockchain projects and experienced Web3 integration, RainbowKit, and Ethereum. One of my last project were NFT minting project. I also built out many mobile apps using React Native. I am a creative & detailed person who writes clean and smart code.

Here you can learn more about my experience.

- · HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, ES6+
- · Node/Express, Python/Django, Ruby on Rails
- · React, Redux(saga | thunk), React Hooks, Next.js, React Native
- · Material UI, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS
- · Postrgres, MySQL, NoSQL, MongoDB
- · Angular 14, PrimeNG, NgRx, RxJs
- · Vue2/3, Vuex, Nuxt.js
- · Figma, Sketch, Zeplin
- Heroku, AWS, GCP, Vercel, Netlify
- · Git, Gitlab, Bitbucket
- · Jira, Trello, Asana

Always open to any challenges and learning new technologies.

Creative & Hard Worker

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Nuremberg, Bavaria, Germany

Jun 2019 - May 2022

## **Senior Frontend Developer**

### Roboyo

- Developed responsive websites and web apps based on UI/UX using React.js
- · React, Redux(saga | thunk), React Hooks, Material UI, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Node/Express
- · Postgres, MySQL, MongoDB
- · Setup Heroku instances and manage pipeline

# Redwood City, California, United States

Jul 2018 - Apr 2019

#### **Frontend Developer**

Dexterity, Inc.

- · Website and web app development using React.js
- · Integrated Chart libraries & implemented Charts using Chart.js, AmCharts and D3.js
- · File uploading to AWS S3 and Google Cloud Storage
- · API integration (REST API & GraphQL)

## Minato, Tokyo, Japan Jul 2012 - Mar 2018

#### **Full Stack Engineer**

BJIT Inc

- Developed static web pages using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and jQuery and PHP.
- · Designed UI/UX using Photoshop and 3DsMax

# **EDUCATION**

Advanced

2008 - 2012 Bachelor's of Computer Science

Tokyo Institute of Technology

 $Specialized\ in\ Computer\ Science.\ Studied\ main\ theories\ of\ computer\ science\ including\ software-design,$ 

project management and Q/A.

LANGUAGES SKILLS

English React/Redux(saga,

thunk)/Next.js/ReactNative

React/Redux(saga, thunk)/Next.js

Japanese Vue, Vuex, Vuetify, Quasar Native

Postgres, MySQL, MongoDB

Web3, NFT, Cryptocurrency, Ethers, Rainbowkit

JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3

Angular, NgRx, RxJs, PrimeNG

Node.js/Express/Nest.js

Material UI, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS